http://thebignote.com/about/the-big-note-privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Awaiting collection, May 2018.
Okay, that’s a fairly serious picture, and, due to the recent changes in legislation, here’s some more serious stuff you need to know about:
Who am I?
Not telling, and anyway quite a few of you know, but you can call me Magicfingers, and this website’s address is: http://thebignote.com.
What personal data is collected and why
The Comments Section
When you leave a comment on this site the data shown in the comments form is collected, and also your IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.  An anonymous string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture, if you have one, is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely.  This is so I can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
If you have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data I hold about you, including any data you have provided to me. You can also request that I erase any personal data I hold about you. This does not include any data obliged to be kept for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Your comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.  Considering that, at the time of writing (5th July 2018), we (it’s your site as much as mine) have been protected from some 566,686 spam comments, you will understand that this is critical to the operation of this website.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on this site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These really are for your convenience, so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment, and they will last for one year.
Embedded content from other websites
Occasionally, articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. the Google Tour Maps). If you choose to view these articles, embedded content from other websites behaves in exactly the same way as if you had visited the other website.  These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.  Got that?
The bottom line is that I do not use, or allow anyone else to use, any data I may have about any of you, and I always ask before using your email address to first contact you, should the need arise.  I thank you.
Feel free to share:Click to email this to a friend (Opens in new window)Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to share on LinkedIn (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pinterest (Opens in new window)Click to print (Opens in new window)
Search for:
Categories
1918 – The Advance East (8)
1919 (1)
Along the River Lys: Comines, Wervik, Geluwe & Menen (11)
Arras (7)
Australia (1)
Belgian Military Cemeteries (2)
Belgian War Memorials (24)
Boesinghe (24)
Brandhoek (4)
Bunkers (33)
Chinese Labour Corps (2)
Demarcation Stones (11)
Diksmuide (3)
Documents, Maps & Artwork (24)
Elverdinge (6)
Etaples (1)
French Flanders (52)
Armentières to La Gorgue (15)
Armentières to Steenwerck (11)
Fromelles (10)
The Nursery: Bois Grenier to Houplines (15)
French War Memorials (14)
Generals (6)
German Military Cemeteries (9)
Headstones (14)
Hill 60 (5)
Ireland (34)
Dublin – The Boer War (1)
Dublin – The Easter Rising (17)
Dublin Cemeteries with Great War Burials (12)
Dublin War Memorials (2)
Langemark (18)
Lizerne (4)
Memorabilia (6)
Messines (31)
Miscellaneous (59)
Museums (10)
Nieuwpoort (7)
Ploegsteert (32)
Ploegsteert Wood (20)
South of Ploegsteert (8)
Poelkapelle (2)
Polygon Wood (4)
Poperinge (10)
Postcards (70)
Potijze (5)
Prisoners-of-War (2)
Ramscappelle & Pervijze (5)
Sanctuary Wood & Hill 62 (5)
Shot at Dawn (25)
Spain (1)
St. Jean (15)
St. Julien (4)
The Belgian Sector (16)
The Menin Road (18)
The Road to Passchendaele – Third Ypres 1917 (20)
The Somme (58)
Albert (2)
Amiens (3)
Thiepval (7)
Villers-Bretonneux (4)
U.K. Churches, Memorials & Cemeteries – Back in Blighty (469)
An Introduction (1)
Cornwall (115)
Derbyshire (6)
Devonshire (74)
Dorset (1)
Essex (4)
Gloucestershire (12)
Hampshire (8)
London (8)
North Wales & Anglesey (6)
Northumberland (21)
Oxfordshire (4)
Scotland (20)
Borders (1)
Highlands (19)
Somerset (34)
Suffolk (3)
Surrey (120)
Brookwood Military Cemetery (2)
Woking Muslim Cemetery (3)
Sussex East (10)
Sussex West (3)
Warwickshire (3)
Wiltshire (10)
Vlamertinge (6)
Weaponry & Relics (29)
Austro-Hungarian Hand Grenades (14)
German Hand Grenades (7)
German Helmets (1)
Wervik & Wervicq-Sud (9)
Wulvergem (7)
Ypres (Ieper) (26)
The Menin Gate (6)
Zandvoorde (5)
Zillebeke (23)
Zonnebeke (5)
Recent Posts
British Military Headstones – Personal Inscriptions
December 9, 2020
British Military Headstones – The Rareties Part Three: A Question of Crosses & Other Variations
December 3, 2020
Ten Years After
November 27, 2020
British Military Headstones – The Rareties Part Two: Duhallow Blocks
November 24, 2020
British Military Headstones – The Rareties Part One: Special Memorials
November 20, 2020
‘Mort pour la France’ – The Headstone of the Unknown Soldier Part Seven
November 12, 2020
Remember the Dead
November 11, 2020
‘Gefallen für Deutschland’ – The Headstone of the Unknown Soldier Part Six
November 8, 2020
‘Known unto God’ – The Headstone of the Unknown Soldier Part Five
November 6, 2020
Virtual Tour & Extra Headstone (snappy title eh?)
November 2, 2020
Recent CommentsGordon Plimmer on British Military Headstones – Personal InscriptionsMagicfingers on British Military Headstones – Personal InscriptionsGordon Plimmer on British Military Headstones – Personal InscriptionsMagicfingers on British Military Headstones – Personal InscriptionsMagicfingers on British Military Headstones – Personal InscriptionsMagicfingers on British Military Headstones – Personal InscriptionsJon T on British Military Headstones – Personal InscriptionsArchives Archives
Select Month
December 2020
November 2020
October 2020
September 2020
August 2020
July 2020
June 2020
Privacy & Cookies: This site uses cookies. By continuing to use this website, you agree to their use.
To find out more, including how to control cookies, see here:
Cookie Policy
With the British Army in Flanders & France
Proudly powered by WordPress.
Send to Email Address
Your Name
Your Email Address
Cancel
Post was not sent - check your email addresses!
Email check failed, please try again
Sorry, your blog cannot share posts by email.
